[
{"question":"TCP/IP model does not have ______ layer but OSI model have this layer.",
"answer":"Session",
"marks":10}
,
{"question":"What is used to identify a process on a host by the transport layer?",
"answer":"Port number",
"marks":10}
,
{"question":"Which 3 protocols are used in accessing the internet? (Answer format: P1, P2, P3 where P indicates protocol)",
"answer":"DHCP, DNS, HTTP",
"marks":10}
,
{"question":"An attempt to make a computer resource unavailable to its intended users is called?",
"answer":"DOS",
"marks":10}
,
{"question":"Which protocol allows clients to update their DNS entry as their IP address changes?",
"answer":"DDNS",
"marks":10}
,
{"question":"What are the network firewalls that can efficiently process packets, but are vulnerable to spoofing attacks?",
"answer":"Packet filtering firewall",
"marks":10}
,
{"question":"A packet-filtering firewall filters packets after it examines them in their entirety. True or false",
"answer":"False",
"marks":10}
,
{"question":"Which network firewall that can block attacks that could reveal protocol vulnerabilities, but require high processing time?",
"answer":"Stateful inspection firewall",
"marks":10}
,
{"question":"A proxy firewall is another name for an application-level gateway. True or false",
"answer":"True",
"marks":10}
,
{"question":"Which networking device forwards data packets between two computer networks?",
"answer":"Router",
"marks":10}
]